Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/bhanugihettiarachchi-1930a0132 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

MySQL

Test Designing

Test Environment Setup

Languages

English

Sinhalese

Bhanugi Hettiarachchi

Associate Consultant - Software Quality at Virtusa Sri Lanka

Summary

Result oriented Software Quality Engineer with extensive experience in API testing in the domain of Insurance. A dedicated, self-motivated and hardworking individual who is willing to learn and adapt to new technologies. Easily collaborate with Developers and Project Managers to accomplish milestones and capable at both working individually or as a team. Have solid history of discovering errors and defects.

Experience

Virtusa

3 years 1 month

Associate Consultant - Software Quality April 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months) Sri Lanka

Software Quality Engineer September 2020 - April 2022 (1 year 8 months) Colombo District, Western, Sri Lanka

SimCentric Technologies
Software Quality Assurance Engineer (Intern)
August 2018 - February 2019 (7 months)

Education

University of Moratuwa

Master of Business Administration (MBA) in Information Technology, Business Analytics · (January 2022)

University of Moratuwa

BSc. (Hons.) in Information Technology and Management (2016 - 2020)

University of Colombo School of Computing
Training Course on Software Quality Assurance Using Test Automation
Frameworks · (2019 - 2019)

National institute of Business Management (NIBM) Diploma in English · (2014 - 2015)